Why did you start smoking?
When you miss someone so much,
you can only try to adopt their habits.
Who is he?
Is it any of your business?
Mr. Gao.
I hope you treat your life well.
Don't give up on it.
My treatment is over.
In what capacity are you telling me this?
Today is Wednesday.
Our Wednesday.
Let's just put an end to this together.
There's no need.
Tell me...
about your personal life recently.
Personal life?
You mean sex, right?
Don't worry.
I have plenty of options without you.
There's one standing right there.
Gao Zhun, can you stop degrading yourself?
You won't sleep with me,
nor let me sleep with others.
What do you want?
I...
Zou Yun.
Let's go home.
I'm hungry.
[Episode 11]
Actually, your place
is very similar to my childhood home.
Are you kidding me?
You live in a mansion.
Your family members are all elites.
You have a prestigious background.
Before becoming an industry elite,
I also lived a simple, ordinary life.
Otherwise, I wouldn't
crave your home-cooked meals
and refuse to leave.
Don't say that.
We are both...
abandoned people.
Are you... still going back to him?
I can't go back.
Or rather...
He doesn't want me anymore.
It's okay.
Life goes on, day by day.
Whatever you want to eat, whatever you like,
just tell me.
I'll make it for you.
Why are you so nice to me?
Well...
Don't you think we're like two stray dogs
sheltering from the rain under one roof?
Cut! That's a wrap!
Change for the next scene.
I'll wait for you tonight.
At the old place.
Mr. Zhang.
Long time no see.
Ms. Qin.
Don't call me that.
Did you know?
We were supposed to have a bed scene.
Unfortunately, Director Chen cut it.
Now Zhen Xin gets to enjoy you,
while I get nothing.
All right, I'm just teasing.
But have you heard about this?
What is it?
The 50 million.
What? You didn't know?
It's about Best Actor Zhen.
To break up with his ex, he spent 50 million.
He gave up money and resources
just to ensure a clean break.
Hey, the director is looking for you.
Over here.
Sorry, I'll head over first.
Dude.
Look at this.
Look.
[50-Million Break Up!
Cashing In For True Love!]
I thought he was just playing with you.
I didn't expect he'd actually be serious.
He actually spent 50 million for you.
Why didn't you come to see me?
Don't worry.
Regardless of whether the news dies down,
I won't break up with you.
- About us...
- Is the 50 million thing true?
Hey, it was just to ensure a clean break.
I couldn't let the girl lose out, could I?
Why didn't you tell me?
If I told you, what if you felt burdened?
What if you thought I was using money
to coerce you into my arms?
What if you end up throwing yourself at me?
Who's throwing themselves at you?
Me.
I'm throwing myself at you.
I've been missing you like crazy.
Zhen Xin.
Wait.
What's wrong with you today?
I managed to sneak out with great difficulty.
Are you really going to fight
with me over the 50 million?
Zhen Xin, are we a couple?
Yes.
But couples talk, eat, fight, and date.
And us?
We don't have any of that.
We don't even discuss things together.
All we seem to have is...
Desire.
Let's go.
To do what?
A date.
A movie.
A midnight screening for couples.
You're crazy.
We have a full schedule of filming tomorrow.
No matter how busy work is,
we still have to date.
Right, darling?
Hey.
Who are you?
Fuck.
[Fang Chi]
You said...
If it weren't for...
Being raped...
I wouldn't have met you.
But isn't it funny?
Zou Yun was the one who raped me.
So, the nightmare never left me.
Even if I replaced the rapist with you,
he would still appear by my side...
And devour me.
Fang Chi.
I'm glad I met you.
Even though you've abandoned me.
Did you...
make all this?
I gave it a try.
But I might have added the wrong seasoning.
It doesn't taste good.
Do you want to try some?
The soup is actually quite fresh.
Don't you think it's bad?
Since you made it,
I'll love it no matter how it tastes.
I didn't know
you were so good at sweet-talking.
But this soup...
I really did make it just for you.
Because I moved in today.
Really?
To be honest,
I thought you were going to leave.
Here, look.
I bought this for you.
I know you only wear high-end things.
So, I went to a luxury store
to buy this for you.
And these...
You prepared these for me too, didn't you?
They're just some sleeping pills.
They'll help you sleep more soundly.
I mean well.
As for those,
they're part of my private collection.
You ruined me.
But didn't you enjoy it too?
How can you say I ruined you?
I'm opening the door to a new world for you.
If it weren't for me,
would you and that doctor
have ever gotten together?
Yeah?
You already got what you wanted.
Why do you still come near me?
Because you're so wonderful.
So wonderful that I can't forget you.
So wonderful that...
I want to savor you one more time.
But after that...
After that time,
you started becoming cautious.
Not only did I not get another chance,
I had to fucking watch
as that doctor reaped the rewards.
Can you go upstairs by yourself?
Yeah.
Is it necessary for two grown men
to say goodbye like that?
Do all rich people have some kind of problem?
What's wrong with liking women?
Yes.
We're from different worlds.
You're in the sky.
I'm in the mud.
Every time you look at me,
it's like you're looking at a stray dog.
So, I want you to submit to me.
Teaching you a lesson was fine.
But who would have thought...
that you'd taste surprisingly good?
You raped me. That's a crime.
But didn't you enjoy it too?
Actually, I'm very, very curious.
Did you and him...
have as much fun as we did?
You're not even worthy of mentioning him.
Is that so?
It seems...
I'll have to help you refresh your memory.
What did you put in the soup?
Are you trying to kill me?
That would be going too easy on you.
I can't beat you, and I can't overpower you.
Only by giving you enough sleeping pills...
can I kill you with my own hands.
You ruined my life.
So, let's go to hell together.
You want to kill me?
Too bad.
I'm strong enough,
so before the drug kicks in...
No...
Before you take your last breath,
I'll give you one last good time.
Stop!
Let go!
Gao Zhun!
Cut! That's a wrap!
Not bad.
Mr. Wu.
Wait a moment, we need a pickup shot
of you going up and down the stairs.
Okay.
After this scene,
I'll be finished with my part.
I'll be leaving.
You can't leave just yet.
Our crew has been trending
on social media lately.
The film festival has sent me an invitation.
The opening red carpet is in two days.
The whole crew will walk it together.
So, get your outfits ready.
That's great news.
I'll be right there with Zhun.
Thank you, Director.
Let me be clear.
The trending topics for the past two days
are all about how you two don't get along.
Our movie is a romance with a happy ending.
We can't have that kind of publicity.
You two must put on
a good show on the red carpet.
What show? That we're a loving couple?
Just some appropriate fan service.
But mind your manners. Don't overdo it.
The live stream might cut you out.
Understood. Mission accepted.
Don't be nervous.
I'm right here.
[ORSYU Film International Festival]
Sign closer. Let's put our names together.
Is that appropriate?
Shouldn't we keep some distance?
Did you forget what Director Chen said?
Just sign it confidently.
Still haven't processed it yet?
It feels a bit surreal.
After all, I've wanted to walk
the red carpet for a long time.
You'll get used to it.
Zhen Xin, something happened.
You two need to leave now.
Get the bodyguards over here.
- What happened?
- Let's get out of here first.
- Go out the back, the car is waiting.
- Yeah.
Stop filming!
Mr. Zhen, Mr. Zhang!
Photos of you two at the cinema
late at night are all over the internet.
Are you two in a relationship?
Is it true, as the rumors say,
that you fell in love while filming?
Everyone, step back! Step back!
Please give us a statement!
Don't push! Move back!
Watch out for your safety!
- Hello?
- Zhun.
Why haven't you called Grandma in so long?
Grandma.
I've been filming.
I've been busy, so I...
Oh.
They've been talking about you on TV lately.
I saw it all.
Is it true?
Zhun.
I don't expect you to bring
great honor to our family,
or to become someone famous.
I just hope you can be safe,
live a steady life, and be happy.
But the way you are now,
are you truly happy?
Grandma, I'm very happy right now.
Happy?
I'm glad you're happy.
As long as you're happy,
when I pass away one day,
I'll be able to face your parents.
Zhun.
- Zhun.
- Grandma.
Are you crying?
Did Grandma say something wrong?
Grandma.
You didn't do anything wrong.
Zhun.
Ignore what others say.
Everyone lives their own life.
It's just that, regarding you and Dan Yi...
Grandma, let me talk to him.
All the neighbors are gossiping.
I really can't stop them.
I'm sorry.
Thank you for staying with my family.
Zhang Zhun.
This is the second time.
You're gambling with everything you have.
Dan Yi.
Come back.
Grandma and I will wait for you at home.
No matter...
No matter what,
I won't be coming back.
I'm sorry.
[Grandma]
Mr. Zhen, blink if you're being
held hostage by this manipulative jerk.
The way he's using this for hype is disgusting.
Zhang Zhun's desperate
social climbing is pathetic.
He's thrown away his dignity
just to get famous.
Zhen Xin used to date only top-tier beauties.
He must be blind to fall for you.
Does he think he's gay
just because he's in a gay movie?
Disgusting marketing. Boycott the movie.
Zhang Zhun, get out of showbiz.
Don't defile our dear Mr. Zhen.
[Comments (9999+)]
[Must be blind to fall for you!]
I'll have my team suppress these comments.
Just like with the 50 million scandal.
Don't be afraid.
The fifth of next month is your birthday.
What do you want for a gift?
Hello, Qin.
Stop talking. I won't agree to it.
Arranging a new fake girlfriend
for me right after a breakup?
Is this PR move any better
than me seeing a movie with a man?
What do you mean we won't work out?
You are you, and we are us.
That's right.
I'm with him now.
We're gay. Are you satisfied now?
What are you doing?
Coming out.
I, Zhen Xin, own up to what I do.
No. Absolutely not.
Why not?
Do you regret it?
No.
I don't regret it.
But you can't come out.
Why can't I?
I can't be that selfish.
I still have my grandma and my family.
You still have me.
Am I supposed to live off you?
Do you have many 50 millions to spare?
Zhen Xin.
Aside from all that,
I have to consider my family.
We're living our own lives.
What does it have to do with them?
This is between us.
My father died young.
My mom died of illness when I was thirteen.
My grandma raised me in a small town.
No matter how hard it was,
I never once saw her cry.
But today, she and I...
Anyway, I don't want her, at her age,
to be unable to hold her head up in public.
She'll get through it.
Think about Gao Zhun and Fang Chi.
They were in such despair,
but didn't they make it through?
We can, too.
That's fiction. It's a fantasy, a script.
It's impossible in real life.
The story is fake, but the feelings are real.
You're too immersed in the role.
I'm too immersed?
Have you forgotten
who called me Fang Chi off-screen?
When?
Do you dare say...
we weren't just acting?
Yes.
We were acting.
There's one week left.
Then, the movie wraps up.
We...
We should snap out of it, too.
Come on, everyone.
Let's review your performance
over the last few days.
We wrap up in four and a half days.
The remaining scenes
are all high-intensity emotional ones.
Things have been a bit chaotic lately.
You're both not in the right headspace.
How about we add a table-read tonight?
To get immersed...
and find the right feeling.
Director Chen, I have plans tonight.
The table-read has to be
during the day or another time.
Zhou Zheng, make the arrangements.
Adjust the schedule.
Let's do the table-read now.
Okay.
Turn to Scene 88.
Let's look at this scene.
[Grandma]
Call Dan Yi even if you're busy.
[We've broken up]
Okay.
I was wrong. I wasn't thinking straight.
Let's do as you say.
We'll be a couple anyway,
so you call the shots.
Do you know what you look like now?
Like a proud panther...
desperately yearning for hugs.
Put your phones away. Table-read time!
Are you just getting back
from an important event?
I do have an important event tonight.
Wait for me. I'll be ready soon.
Zhang Zhun.
Are you...
willing to spend the rest of your life with me?
Is this how he is planning to confess?
The passcode... could it be my birthday?